(Raj:)Boy, I'm so hungry today.
(Raj:)I wonder why?
(Howard:)Because you had sex the other night?
(Raj:)You know what?
(Raj:)That may be it.
(Raj:)By the way,
it isn't like riding a bike.
(Raj:)Like, I fell off a few times.
(Leonard:)-Hey, buddy.
-Hello.
(Leonard:)You okay?
(Sheldon:)I just got called
into President Siebert's office.
(Sheldon:)The university
won't let me switch my field
(Sheldon:)of study to inflationary
cosmology.
(Sheldon:)They're forcing me
to continue with string theory.
(Raj:)-Why?
-He said it's why they hired me,
(Sheldon:)it's what my grant
was designated for,
(Sheldon:)and that everybody has to
do things they don't want to do.
(Sheldon:)He then gave an example
of something he had to do,
(Sheldon:)even though he didn't want to,
which was look at my stupid face.
(Leonard:)That's a rude thing to say out loud.